Jakiri Gamboa

3527 Shadowmeadows Dr., Houston, TX 77082 (Desired work location - Houston, Tx) jgamboa929@gmail.com (Resume Links Available On Portfolio Site)

Portfolio Site portfolio-jg.surge.sh | GitHub https://github.com/jg00

SUMMARY

Involved with the reporting needs of clinicians for +5 years building rapport with clients, performing data analysis/gathering, and writing complex T-SQL queries. I enjoy learning to code and decided to take a step forward in my career as an aspiring Full Stack Web Developer focused on but not limited to JavaScript web technologies React, Express, Node.js, and MongoDb. I graduated from DigitalCrafts' coding bootcamp January 2019.

EDUCATION

University of Houston, Houston, TX. Graduated Fall 2002.

Bachelor of Business Administration - Major in Management Information Systems.

SKILLS

- · Frontend JavaScript, React, CSS, HTML
- Backend & Databases Node.js, Express.js, Microsoft T-SQL
- Reporting Tools and Others SAP Crystal Reports, Microsoft SSRS

CERTIFICATIONS

DigitalCrafts - Full-Stack Immersive Program. Sep 2018 to Jan 2019

 Immersive software engineering training course covering full-stack development including, but not limited to JavaScript, Python, including an emphasis on cutting-edge frameworks like React/Redux and serverside technologies including Node.js, Express, and PostgreSQL.

EPIC Clarity Data Model

· Beacon (Oncology), Radiant/Cupid (Imaging/CathLab), Optime/Anesthesia (OR)

FEATURED PROJECTS (Resume Links Available On Portfolio Site)

Nama Chocolates (React Full Stack Project)

- Initial attempt to create a React shopping cart with the admin, non-admin and anonymous users in mind.
- The project was created using React, Redux, Bootstrap 4 for the frontend. The backend technologies included MongoDb, Express.js, Node.js, JSON Web Tokens, and Stripe API.
- · Live Demo | Nama Shopping Cart on Heroku | GitHub

My Portfolio Site (with more projects)

- · Created a mobile responsive site using CSS Flexbox.
- Portfolio Site | GitHub
- · Other projects Pool Table Management App (Python), Grand Hotel (CSS), Simple Weather (JS, CSS), etc.

MJ Burgers (React Frontend Project)

- Created MJ-Burgers frontend site using React class and functional components. The site lets the user dynamically add ingredients to build their burger.
- MJ Burgers Site | GitHub

WORK EXPERIENCE

Clinical Decision Support Specialist II. Houston Methodist. Houston, TX. 03/19/2012 - 08/24/2018

- · Responsible for the report development needs of clinicians, managers, directors, etc. from EPIC System.
- Primary Crystal Reports developer for Beacon (Oncology) and Radiant/Cupid (Imaging) modules.

Technical Support. RealEC Technologies. Houston, TX. 09/2008 - 03/2012

 Responsible for the ad-hoc reporting needs of the support team manager and performed configuration updates as requested by client configuration team utilizing T-SQL.

Database Analyst. American Productivity Quality Center. Houston, TX. 08/2007 - 06/2008

Responsible for the survey creation process and survey refreshes.

Technical Analyst. Fulbright & Jaworski, LLP. Houston, TX. 04/2004 - 07/2007

· Responsible for maintenance and administration of the firm's Litigation Document Management System.

Repair Technician. Foxconn. Houston, TX. 09/2003 - 04/2004

· Refurbished laptops and desktops at assembly line.

MS Access Contractor. The Park People. Houston, TX. 12/2003 - 01/2004

Developed Access database forms and reports for tracking members and donations.

Work Study Intern. Katy Prairie Conservancy. Houston, TX. 09/2002 - 02/2003

Developed Access database form and reports for tracking members and donations.